Aleksandr Andrukhov

Sex: Male

Date of birth: 1997-02-12

Present Contact Address: Moscow, Russia

Permanent Contact Address: Rostov-On-Don, Russia

Nationality: Russian

Email: drammtv@gmail.com

Github: github.com/AlertRED

LinkedIn:

inkedin.com/in/andrukhov-

aleksandr

WORK EXPERIENCE

KALABI - Backend developer

Dec 2022 - Apr 2023

Moscow, Russia

Development the API service in python. Flask, Flask-restplus, sqlalchemy, pytest, Redis, Postgresql, docker-compose technologies were used. Vue + typescript were also used for frontend. I was adding and expanding existing functionality, writing unit tests, and integrating with third-party services. Periodically worked with Docker-Compose and the frontend part of the project.

• Infotecs Internet Trust - Backend developer

Dec 2021 - Jul 2022

Moscow, Russia

Support for Legacy on Django and TypeScript and FastAPI a little bit, development of new functionality, also Pytest, Docker, Redis, RabbitMQ were used.

• FabLite - Backend developer

Nov 2020 - Oct 2021

Novosibirsk, Russia

Writing a REST API using FastAPI, developing sites using Flask, Django, writing documentation, working with Redis.

• **2-up** – Backend developer

Apr 2019 - Aug 2019

Rostov-On-Don, Russia

PHP backend development - REST API writing, website parsing. Knowledge in Linux and SQL was applied.

EDUCATION

Harbin Institute of Technology, Computer Science - M.Sc. (in English)
 Sep 2019 - Jul
 2022

GPA: 88.4/100.0

• **Don State Technical University,** Software Engineering - B.Sc.

Rostov-On-Don, Russia

Sep 2015 - Jul

GPA: 4.42/5.0, **Final State Examination:** 5.0/5.0, **Graduation Thesis:**

4.0/5.0

Relevant Coursework: Databases, Web-technologies, Object-oriented programming, Programming of mobile devices.

RESEARCH

Recognition and measurement of vehicle speed in complex weather conditions

2022

A system based on deep learning to recognize vehicles on the roads in bad weather conditions. The system also calculates the transport speed using a special positioning algorithm.

Object recognition in a video stream

2019

The purpose of this paper is to simplify viewing of the traffic of objects in a video stream by identifying them using an object recognition application; presents algorithms for the implementation of the application. The source code

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Linux, Python3, Flask, FastAPI, Django, Vue3, SqlAlchemy, SOLID, SQL, Git, RabbitMQ, Redis

HONOR

2019 - Winner of Chinese Government Scholarship for Master Degree Program (3000 RMB/month stipend; exempt from registration fee, tuition fee, accommodation fee)

LANGUAGES

Russian - Mother language English - B1 for the modules is written in Python using the accompanying libraries.

- Attack on information with the technologies of social engineering International scientific and technical conference «System analysis, control and information processing» (SAC&IP)
 This article explores the technology of social engineering as an attack on information, as well as its main methods and highlights the ways in which they are used.
- Cluster analysis and basic algorithms of data clustering –
 International scientific and technical conference «System
 analysis, control and information processing» (SAC&IP), 2017
 The analysis and sorting technology as clusterization are investigated, its main algorithms were analyzed. The main problems examined: how great is the effectiveness of the current clustering algorithms and theirs trends in the development.

SUMMARY

I am doing backend development in Python. The total experience in this programming language is more than 5 years. I try to stick to SOLID and KISS. In between jobs, I always do some pet project of my own and work freelance. I will be happy to learn something new (programming language, framework, technology, etc.). I am also interested in the field of data engineering.

I welcome relocation to another country or work remotely. The current English is at the B1 level and now I am actively working on improving it.